Antoine Beaugas: Hello, everyone!
John Hazlewood: Hello, Antoine. Hello, everybody.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Hello, Mr. John, how are you doing?
John Hazlewood: It's, Tuesday, that means Happy Tuesday!
John Hazlewood: Happy Tuesday, everybody!
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Happy Tuesday, Mr. John.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So…
John Hazlewood: So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh my gosh.
John Hazlewood: Happy Sunday is a little bit more of, like, a…
John Hazlewood: Something that people say, I mean, kind of…
John Hazlewood: More than the rest of the days of the week, so I just wanted to…
John Hazlewood: I know we kind of… I understand you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I do understand you, Mr. John. I think I'm the one who asked you before about that, like, what is the happy day? So, yeah, happy Tuesday, guys, and hopefully, happy.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm not sure, because, to be honest, guys, I'm not that happy.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm short on money right now, so I'm not that happy, to be honest. So, yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: What do you think, Antoine, about the happiness?
Antoine Beaugas: Oh, that's…
Antoine Beaugas: I don't think… Anything.
Antoine Beaugas: What do you want me to do?
mohamed abdelmohsen: the.
Antoine Beaugas: Think about happiness.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You know, if you ask me about happiness, I'm gonna let you dollars.
mohamed abdelmohsen: This is heavens for me.
Antoine Beaugas: Oh…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: I mean, that's…
mohamed abdelmohsen: What is happening for you? Like, what? What?
Antoine Beaugas: reader.
mohamed abdelmohsen: that you can see.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh my gosh. Without money, you can't have your freedom. So at the end of the day, you need money to have your freedom. So I'm done.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Anyway.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay. I'm so sorry for interrupting. It's your team now.
Antoine Beaugas: No, no, I'm getting my things ready, so don't worry.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Take your time…
Antoine Beaugas: I have things to show.
John Hazlewood: Antoine is Mr. Freedom. That's why he came to Lemnos and E R.
John Hazlewood: He lived in a village with 200 people in the middle of the island.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Alright, guys.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, he has some beach near him, but…
John Hazlewood: I mean, you come to an island, a Greek island, you want to kind of live near the beach, close to the beach, on the beach, I mean…
John Hazlewood: But… Yeah, we had that conversation Antoine is just kind of.
John Hazlewood: I mean.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, a village with 200 people is… Like.
John Hazlewood: That's good.
John Hazlewood: Some people need a little more energy. There's a girl that kind of… she's moved here.
John Hazlewood: from Thessaloniki to teach.
John Hazlewood: In Madras.
John Hazlewood: Which is, like, the second largest Village… In Limnos.
John Hazlewood: She's gonna teach at, I don't know, high school, some school…
John Hazlewood: And yeah, she decided to live in Medina and drive half an hour every day.
John Hazlewood: To go to Mudros, because… She wanted to live in a…
John Hazlewood: She's young, she said she's young, and she… she doesn't want to live, you know, in a…
John Hazlewood: Small village, I mean… You know, so… Awesome.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's actually a good thing, Mr. John. I didn't try it before, especially in Lemnos. So Antoine, man, I need to ask you this question like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Mister John said, like, you do have, like, kind of 200 people there in Lemnos.
mohamed abdelmohsen: How you can have fun about the parties, the nosiest people, like… Did you meet anyone?
John Hazlewood: That's 200 people in the village where Antoine lives.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, it's not fun.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, the island has about 17,000 people.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh my gosh. Yes, I mean the village that, Antoine… did you meet anyone? Like, you have… there's kind of these parties, like, you have this party on Saturday or Friday, I'm not sure when, like, weekly party in the village, everyone attend, boys, girls, and…
Antoine Beaugas: I'm not a party guy.
John Hazlewood: Antoine.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh, absolutely.
Antoine Beaugas: short period.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You are a good man, Antoine. You are a good man, Antoine.
John Hazlewood: Antoine is a gamer.
John Hazlewood: He's a gamer. He likes to… He's playing…
Antoine Beaugas: We're only 7?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Mmhm.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, I think this… this… this is quite, relieving, because, if I came in the future to the lab. then my fiance will not kill me.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So.
mohamed abdelmohsen: She gonna say, there is no girls, no one on the beach, so you are in the safe side, so yeah, you can go.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Anything else? If she smell, you know, if she smell, actually, like, anything about girl up there.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm gonna be dead, so… Thank you, Antoine, to let me know that.
John Hazlewood: During Thursday, non-fun.
John Hazlewood: Stay single.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay.
John Hazlewood: I have, yeah, we have some people missing here.
John Hazlewood: Mohammed, do you want to…
mohamed abdelmohsen: 6.
John Hazlewood: Reach out to whoever.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, Mr. John.
John Hazlewood: We can get started.
Antoine Beaugas: Burhan Mohammed, it would take quite a long time to contact everyone.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, you can start, you can start.
Antoine Beaugas: Oh yeah? Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Mister.
Antoine Beaugas: Ellen.
Antoine Beaugas: I share my screen because I have things to show.
Antoine Beaugas: Up.
Antoine Beaugas: First of all, So, I've been contacted by Jackie.
Antoine Beaugas: Because he has class during this time.
Antoine Beaugas: So that means he can't, he can't participate in the IoT meeting anymore?
Antoine Beaugas: So I'd like to know if it's possible to move the meeting for him, or if we keep it like that.
John Hazlewood: I think we can move it if it's…
John Hazlewood: We can accommodate everybody else and him.
Antoine Beaugas: Because you want to be in every meetings, and since I don't know
Antoine Beaugas: When the other meetings are, because there's quite a lot.
John Hazlewood: Well, just look on the events calendar. Yeah. Everything's there.
John Hazlewood: We can schedule it wherever there's not an events…
John Hazlewood: However, there's not a current meeting.
John Hazlewood: We'll probably need… Say…
John Hazlewood: You know, let's say, plan, you know, maximum an hour and a half for this meeting, and then have a 30-minute
John Hazlewood: And then another meeting can start after that, so…
Antoine Beaugas: you.
John Hazlewood: In between, if we start this, have…
John Hazlewood: Two hours before the next meeting starts.
John Hazlewood: Or if it's… if it's before another meeting, there should be, depending on which meeting it is.
John Hazlewood: Either an hour, an hour and a half.
John Hazlewood: Some meetings are about an hour.
John Hazlewood: They have team meetings.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, so I look at the calendar, and I will do like Spencer did for the Humanoid team. I will ask.
Antoine Beaugas: The team members to post.
Antoine Beaugas: in the IoT channel, their time zone.
Antoine Beaugas: So I can choose a time that accommodates as much people as possible.
Antoine Beaugas: So I'll send a message in the channel, but I'm seeing it right now.
Antoine Beaugas: Please post your time zone in the UTC format.
Antoine Beaugas: in the IoT Discord channel.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So let's start then.
Antoine Beaugas: I have to share my screen, like I said.
Antoine Beaugas: share.
Antoine Beaugas: Up.
Antoine Beaugas: Then.
Antoine Beaugas: This… Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So first about project management since
Antoine Beaugas: There's a lot of new members coming.
Antoine Beaugas: I can't manage everything like that, as I was doing until now. So what I did is, in the team home.
Antoine Beaugas: I added a team assignment here that you can toggle.
Antoine Beaugas: And basically, it's the members.
Antoine Beaugas: with their current tasks I assigned to them, they're working on.
Antoine Beaugas: The hardware they have?
Antoine Beaugas: What other teams they are in, and if they are full-time or not.
Antoine Beaugas: So, it allows me to follow what the team is doing, basically.
Antoine Beaugas: And depending on if the member has a lot of team and is full-time or not, it helps me knowing
Antoine Beaugas: If I can give them a huge task, or if I have to split the task. Into subtasks, or give it to someone else.
Antoine Beaugas: So, same thing, I will send a message in the IoT channel, but what I want…
Antoine Beaugas: Everyone to do is go on the team home.
Antoine Beaugas: So, for those who… Don't know how to get there.
Antoine Beaugas: From Flo Fish, you have the list here, and it's Internet of Things Team Home Up.
Antoine Beaugas: So, go there.
Antoine Beaugas: and you will Put your other teams, yourself.
Antoine Beaugas: And check if what I put for you is right or wrong, and correct. And also, for full-time.
Antoine Beaugas: You just click on it, you have a…
Antoine Beaugas: You have options, you're up, you see?
Antoine Beaugas: And if you have an ESP, so 32S3,
Antoine Beaugas: or the Raspberry Pi 0 2 W.
Antoine Beaugas: Put it, also.
Antoine Beaugas: And it will help me, and also future team leads. when I'll be… when I leave, to, well, manage the team, basically. And I put it here, like that, it's public information, and anybody can check it.
Antoine Beaugas: So yeah, I did that.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Then, let's start with the… the tasks. So, as always, I will begin by me.
Antoine Beaugas: To keep things starting, to have things starting.
Antoine Beaugas: So… I continued working on the diagrams.
Antoine Beaugas: Unfortunately, I wanted to finish…
Antoine Beaugas: this one, it's the ESP state diagram. I wanted to finish it before the meeting, but… It's almost finished.
Antoine Beaugas: It looks like that.
Antoine Beaugas: To show you what it was before?
Antoine Beaugas: This was it.
Antoine Beaugas: And this is the diagram for all of Kaipu.
Antoine Beaugas: So the SP
Antoine Beaugas: the ESP and the Raspberry. It's just a copy-paste from ChatGPT, I suppose, like, they surely asked ChatGPT, give us the state diagram, and they just copy-pasted it, because that's typically what ChatGPT gives you.
Antoine Beaugas: This, and here also.
Antoine Beaugas: So for this one, I've been working with Ash.
Antoine Beaugas: And I am currently finishing it.
Antoine Beaugas: I've started the Raspberry, state, also, diagram.
Antoine Beaugas: But I saw some errors on it, so I'm finishing it before.
Antoine Beaugas: So on the new version of the document, it shows up like this.
Antoine Beaugas: And you can, by pressing Ctrl on your keyboard, you can zoom.
Antoine Beaugas: And you can move around.
Antoine Beaugas: And it updates automatically.
Antoine Beaugas: So, before, it wasn't like that. I've been working some more, you see, and it's what I get here.
Antoine Beaugas: So, that's… that's very useful. You don't have to put an image every time. You just work on the diagram, and…
Antoine Beaugas: It's updated.
Antoine Beaugas: I have one diagram, though, that I can present to you, that I have finished. It's the block diagram.
Antoine Beaugas: I'd like to open it in… Drew you.
Antoine Beaugas: So, before it was like this…
Antoine Beaugas: It's very bad. It shouldn't have been accepted.
Antoine Beaugas: As a diagram, but whatever.
Antoine Beaugas: And now it's like this.
Antoine Beaugas: with colors. It's It's more readable.
Antoine Beaugas: So let's get over it.
Antoine Beaugas: You have three subsystems for Kaipu. You have the power subsystem.
Antoine Beaugas: The Raspberry subsystem And the ESP32 subsystem.
Antoine Beaugas: You have, for the poorer subsystem.
Antoine Beaugas: the USB-C input that goes into the power management integrated circuits that I chose.
Antoine Beaugas: It's connected to the battery.
Antoine Beaugas: And connected to the battery, there's also the fuel gauge that allows the ESP to read the battery level, like 50%, 20%, and so on.
Antoine Beaugas: From the power management integrated circuit, there's a power path. That means when you recharge the battery.
Antoine Beaugas: It is not directly connected to the system.
Antoine Beaugas: For security reason.
Antoine Beaugas: So the circuit gives us between 3.5 volts and 4.2 volts.
Antoine Beaugas: Is the main bus that powers the ESP?
Antoine Beaugas: And it sends.
Antoine Beaugas: voltage to the boost regulator.
Antoine Beaugas: That has been changed, also, for 5 volts, and this is…
Antoine Beaugas: This is for the Raspberry Pi.
Antoine Beaugas: Those components are… can be controlled by the ESP via I2C. This is the red dots, you can see.
Antoine Beaugas: And you can turn on and off the boost regulator.
Antoine Beaugas: with the ESP directly.
Antoine Beaugas: It's so you can cut off the Raspberry Pi completely, and you don't waste power, and it saves a lot of battery.
Antoine Beaugas: With the ESP, you have the touch sensor, the LEDs…
Antoine Beaugas: You have the ADC amplifier that sends the sound to the speaker to make Kapo talk.
Antoine Beaugas: And you have the microphone.
Antoine Beaugas: for Kaipu to hear the user.
Antoine Beaugas: These are… these use HUS.
Antoine Beaugas: In blue.
Antoine Beaugas: It's a communication protocol.
Antoine Beaugas: And for the communication between the Raspberry and the ESP, you have another communication protocol, which is called UART. It's like that, UART.
Antoine Beaugas: And the Raspberry has the camera, the microSD for storage, and it communicates with the mobile application.
Antoine Beaugas: So this is the new, cleaner, and updated block diagram for Kaipo with the new components I chose.
Antoine Beaugas: And before it was like that.
Antoine Beaugas: So, same thing, it should be here, you see?
Antoine Beaugas: And you can zoom and move around.
Antoine Beaugas: So by… so until next Tuesday, I should be… finished with both State diagrams.
Antoine Beaugas: And that will unlock further programmation on the ESP and Raspberry Pi.
Antoine Beaugas: So, it will be my priority for now.
Antoine Beaugas: And I've also… so I selected the…
Antoine Beaugas: The new components that I put.
Antoine Beaugas: In the task, fix and update KPOS documentation, I put them here.
Antoine Beaugas: For the power supply, for the boost converter, for the fuel gauge.
Antoine Beaugas: And I said why I chose them each time.
Antoine Beaugas: And I, I don't remember where it is…
Antoine Beaugas: I… here. In the new documentation, I updated the formation.
Antoine Beaugas: And I put directly the link here.
Antoine Beaugas: Like that, when you read the documentation, you don't have to open a tab and search it yourself. You can directly click on the link in the documentation, and you have it. It's way more practical for everyone.
Antoine Beaugas: So I did it.
Antoine Beaugas: So that's the work I've been doing this week.
Antoine Beaugas: up. Let's go back here.
Antoine Beaugas: So now, I'll ask the others to report.
Antoine Beaugas: And I'm very happy to have done that, because it's way easier now.
Antoine Beaugas: So, Ash is not here. Is Ash here or not? He said he had an issue.
Antoine Beaugas: No, he's not here, okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So… Sosina, research how to reduce the Raspberry booting time.
Antoine Beaugas: With Eichel.
Sosina: Can you hear me?
Antoine Beaugas: Not loud enough.
Sosina: Turn off my camera so that I can be close to my mic.
John Hazlewood: I'm sorry, we still can't hear you. Antoine, maybe can you stop sharing your screen?
John Hazlewood: Yes.
John Hazlewood: Thank you, thank you.
Sosina: No.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, talk a bit, we'll see, but it's a bit low.
Sosina: I'll try to be louder.
Sosina: So let me share my screen for the research I made.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, it's usually like this, Sosina. I don't know, you might want to like hear one of the recordings so you can see. It's just kind of.
John Hazlewood: It's not that loud. There might be some internal settings or something, either with Zoom or your own mic or something that might be able to turn up the volume, but we can hear you okay for now. It's just, like I said, it's just kind of low.
Sosina: Okay, I will work on it.
Sosina: I will try to fix it for next time.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Thank.
Sosina: Try to fix it for next time.
John Hazlewood: Are you going to share your screen and show us something Sosina?
Sosina: Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: So in the meantime, let me ask, have you Sosina and Michael worked together on this or not?
Sosina: Pardon, please?
Antoine Beaugas: Did you and Michael work together?
Antoine Beaugas: on this task.
Sosina: No, I worked alone.
Michael Ballantyne: Yeah, we have a… Time contact with each other yet.
Antoine Beaugas: And did you do you have anything to to report Michael on this task?
Michael Ballantyne: Oh, well.
Michael Ballantyne: You guys can still hear and see me, yes?
Sosina: Adrian, can you see my screen?
Michael Ballantyne: System update, we found updates.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, there's lots of things, okay.
Michael Ballantyne: Thanks.
Michael Ballantyne: Oh, come back here.
Michael Ballantyne: Just a second, I'm about to do a system update.
Michael Ballantyne: Over an hour?
Michael Ballantyne: Repeat that time.
Michael Ballantyne: And we need 4 h.
Michael Ballantyne: Okay, I've looked into the assignment, and…
Michael Ballantyne: I want to spend a little bit more time looking further into it.
Michael Ballantyne: So The the.
Antoine Beaugas: I've seen.
Michael Ballantyne: Kind of surface level.
Antoine Beaugas: What are your other teams? You're in Humanoid, I know that, and do you have other teams?
Michael Ballantyne: No, I also work I have a job. So that's kind of why.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, so you're part-time in the company.
Michael Ballantyne: Yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, Sosina, can you… so, not read everything, of course, but have, like.
Antoine Beaugas: Shortly, what can be done?
Sosina: Okay.
Sosina: So based on the research I made the best research that was made for reducing the time.
Sosina: But I got this… a project called Solar Compact. So, they had a camera with a solar system.
Sosina: Like they tried to minimize the amount of power that Raspberry Pi uses. But apparently they ended up like.
Sosina: It was the same, like, in addition to minimizing the power, they ended up reducing the time from 12 seconds to 3.5 seconds to reduce the…
Sosina: The time of the Raspberry Pi booting, so…
Sosina: To like, make it general. They had like 12 steps to do.
Sosina: That we should do in order to make it,
Sosina: 7 seconds less, as the same as this.
Sosina: But in general, like, they did 3 main things.
Sosina: So like when there is verified boots. It looks for every hardware part. If it's connected with other like, if it's used or not.
Sosina: So instead of doing that, they created create a text file that's called config.
Sosina: And.
Sosina: They specifically
Sosina: Fix it what they are looking for. So, they stopped, the screen… Just researching the overview.
Sosina: The, like, the display searching… systems on the… Raspberry Pi?
Sosina: and also the the second thing they did is they're like unnecessary loading files. After mounting the Sd card, they are like
Sosina: Zip the unnecessary files, so they tried to remove those cards after mounting them.
Sosina: And then it's hopeless as well. And the last one, which is
Sosina: More essential is they try to make the kernel smoother.
Sosina: Instead of like.
Sosina: making everything, every process running on the Raspberry Pi. They try to minimize the tasks, the carnel inside the carnel, so that they build their own
Sosina: kernel, and then they left it with like most of the time the kernel is zipped, but they left it unzipped because for the CPU to function and process
Sosina: this what is on the kernel it has to unpack again so to minimize the time that's
Sosina: To minimize the time of unpacking, they also reduced the time, so, like.
Sosina: I'm, like, listed everything I received to do, and the content of the… Text file on this.
Sosina: Page of… The notion to make it short like it it has it has a con.
Sosina: I specified what each step does and what, how many, seconds it reduces.
Sosina: So if you want me to continue with that, I can, but to make you sure, this is everything, Jamie.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, that's great. Have you sourced your findings with a link or something?
Sosina: Yeah, yeah, I also.
Sosina: I also put that… Here, down after the 12 steps.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, wow, okay, wow, that's great.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, I like that.
Antoine Beaugas: Great, thank you, Sosina.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, so…
Antoine Beaugas: I don't think we need to work on that anymore. I'll have to go over it to check everything, of course, and validate the task as completed.
Antoine Beaugas: Hopefully.
Antoine Beaugas: So… For now… Let's see… I will assign you… with… Ash.
Antoine Beaugas: You remember the handover… the… how is it called? The handover of the connection protocol?
Sosina: Yeah, yeah, I do.
Antoine Beaugas: You will work with ACT for Pro…
Antoine Beaugas: programming, well, putting the Workweek program into ESP-IDF on VS Code.
Antoine Beaugas: Following the… The structure we have.
Antoine Beaugas: And, when it will be done, I'll be able to test it on my hardware.
Antoine Beaugas: So, I don't know what Ash did, because he doesn't have a lot of time, because of his studies.
Antoine Beaugas: So… First, contact him.
Antoine Beaugas: And… help him, basically, do that. Together, you will put your code on VS Code.
Antoine Beaugas: And the objective is that I just flash it and test.
Sosina: Okay, I can see them in a minute.
Sosina: configured.
Antoine Beaugas: So, you already have sent this task because you created it, so you won't have a notification.
Antoine Beaugas: So just, don't forget about it, basically.
Sosina: Sorry.
Antoine Beaugas: Then let's see.
Antoine Beaugas: And.
Antoine Beaugas: Yes, so, Michael, again, for you.
Antoine Beaugas: And Charles was on it also, but Charles isn't here.
Antoine Beaugas: No, he… he isn't here.
Antoine Beaugas: So, Michael, the task.
Antoine Beaugas: Raspberry Pi backend communication. You remember this one? For… Searching how to use the Raspberry to send data to the… to the AI.
Michael Ballantyne: Yeah.
Michael Ballantyne: I haven't looked much into it, because I've been Busy.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Since, the task to reduce the Raspberry booting time seems to be completed.
Antoine Beaugas: You can resume this one, the backend.
Michael Ballantyne: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So Charlie's in here. Jackie's in here.
Antoine Beaugas: Who is the who is here? Chibu Ezekiel
Antoine Beaugas: Even with the lists, there's still a lot of… okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Size name, new member, new member…
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, that's it. So the other members are are quite new. So
Antoine Beaugas: I have a question for all of you Chibuike, sorry if I mispronounce your name Chibuike Chizalum and Hasnai
Antoine Beaugas: I'd like to know where you're at for your IoT Masterclass.
Antoine Beaugas: And if you have been assigned a module.
Antoine Beaugas: Or if you only have the masterclass.
HASNAE: Yes, hello everyone.
Antoine Beaugas: Hi.
HASNAE: I did finish my master class, last week, and you assigned me with two modules.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, unfortunately.
HASNAE: The medium one and the advanced one, I finished them this week.
HASNAE: And you assigned me with a task of search for a simulator, as we were talking about it.
HASNAE: Last week I was looking for one, I'm not sure I found one. I found one, but I'm not very sure it's going to be working, so I needed to.
HASNAE: I need to test it myself and I need your help with.
HASNAE: the… the list Of the last list of all the materials.
HASNAE: modules we need for the projects, for me to try to integrate them myself and look if the projects can be simulated with this one, this simulator I found, or I need to look for another one.
HASNAE: So that's was for me this week and.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, can I look at the task real quick, or do I have to search it somewhere?
Antoine Beaugas: Task.
HASNAE: I… I didn't write anything, any…
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, you didn't write… okay.
HASNAE: Yeah, I didn't give any feedback, because I… the simulator is already written on the Notion page you give me as a reference, but I don't know why it wasn't taken in consideration.
HASNAE: So that's why I wanted for you to give me or to make me know where are the components, the list or the last one. I wanted the last one because I went through the document.
HASNAE: station, and I get confused, because there are a lot of resources for the CAICO projects that I don't know what are the last versions of the material.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So we.
HASNAE: And.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, we'll make that clearer, okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Do you remember the name of the simulator you found and you want to test?
HASNAE: Yeah, yeah, yes, yes, yes, I have it right now in front of me. Velxio. V-E-L-X-I-O.
HASNAE: Vixio.
HASNAE: He got the ESP32 and also the Raspberry. What was its name? Raspberry Pi Pico.
HASNAE: 2W, but the other ones, I'm not sure for the other ones, because they, as written on the page.
HASNAE: We had a problem with the voice recording.
HASNAE: That's why I'm not sure if it is gonna be working or not, but the other components, I think, they can be… they can be…
HASNAE: Introduced, or… they can be added.
HASNAE: Easily.
HASNAE: Hopefully.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, yeah, so… don't hesitate, even if you're not sure, just so that the other members know what is currently being done on the task.
Antoine Beaugas: To put, the link of the simulator on the task, because you're… Okay, now…
Antoine Beaugas: There are 5 members assigned to it, so…
HASNAE: 5-minute.
Antoine Beaugas: So if you look at the task, I just wrote, like, candidates, I'll put the link.
Antoine Beaugas: Just that, the bare minimum.
Antoine Beaugas: And… after you try it.
HASNAE: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: you think.
HASNAE: It's.
Antoine Beaugas: It's not, it's not very usable. You write why, like…
HASNAE: will…
Antoine Beaugas: Why is it not usable? And so on.
HASNAE: business models.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah.
HASNAE: To say it's not, I need the material.
HASNAE: lists.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, also, yeah.
HASNAE: Yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: Are you… I'll write it on the…
HASNAE: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: On my, assignment list, are you full-time or not?
HASNAE: I am actually a student, but I don't have a lot of.
Antoine Beaugas: you.
HASNAE: What? Sorry?
Antoine Beaugas: Oh, you're a student, yes, so you're…
HASNAE: Sorry, boss.
Antoine Beaugas: Full time.
HASNAE: Yeah, I am student, but I am last year, so I don't have a lot of classes.
HASNAE: I have 3 months, 4 months left for me to graduate, so I don't have.
HASNAE: A lot of classes to attend to.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay. Yeah, she's full time.
John Hazlewood: HASANES full time.
Antoine Beaugas: So what we'll do is we'll meet, sometime.
HASNAE: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: And we will work on it together. I'll be able to show you the components.
Antoine Beaugas: What you're missing, we'll see, we'll see together.
HASNAE: Okay, okay.
HASNAE: I will wait for you to send me a message or something?
Antoine Beaugas: Yes, yes. I'll send you a message on Discord.
HASNAE: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So then… Chibuiki, what about you?
Chibuike Ezekiel: Sorry.
Chibuike Ezekiel: Yes, I've started on my master classes.
Chibuike Ezekiel: Though I will have finished it last week, I was a bit too busy with schoolwork, but I should be able to… I'll be able to finish it this week, and you've also assigned some modules to me, and…
Chibuike Ezekiel: I'll… I'll start… start this week soon.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, have you been assigned.
Chibuike Ezekiel: the.
Antoine Beaugas: some modules for the masterclass or not?
Antoine Beaugas: Do you remember?
Chibuike Ezekiel: Yes, yes.
Antoine Beaugas: So do the master class before any task.
Chibuike Ezekiel: something.
Antoine Beaugas: So don't worry about the research task.
Antoine Beaugas: focus.
Chibuike Ezekiel: the.
Antoine Beaugas: guess.
Chibuike Ezekiel: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So then.
Antoine Beaugas: Chizalum Chizalum.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Yeah. Yeah. Try it. Just call me Victor. The name is hard.
Antoine Beaugas: Ha ha ha ha.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Yeah.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: I just finished my master class about two days ago, so I've just been busy with some schoolwork, but I've actually gone through the module I was assigned about researching for a simulator.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: So, I'll say that, like, what exactly… I've not, like, gone through it properly anyway, but…
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: maybe I would like, maybe, certain things I need to test in each simulator I, like, go across, or, like, get across, because I just say, okay, let me, like, use AI as, like, research, like, different simulators first, get a list, and then I want to, like, have a better idea of what I'm meant to test in these simulators.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, well… For your research, you can use any tool.
Antoine Beaugas: And so, yeah, I haven't wrote it in the test, but you're allowed to select a paid simulator, if necessary.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So don't… if you see it costs some money, don't block on it, like.
Antoine Beaugas: Of course, don't write yourself.
Antoine Beaugas: It would be… it would be a pity to lose some money over it, but, like, do some research over it, even if it's a paid simulator.
Antoine Beaugas: And so… so you can use any tool for your research, AI, to have a list, or something. You can search on their website, usually there's some information.
Antoine Beaugas: Maybe some videos on YouTube, for instance?
Antoine Beaugas: Sometimes, some people present the simulator.
Antoine Beaugas: And the third best is to try it, if you can try it for free.
Antoine Beaugas: dive into it a bit, see what's possible, and so on. And so, write for each simulator, write on the task.
Antoine Beaugas: What you found out, basically.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Okay.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Well, it's like, let me see…
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: pertaining to Skype or not, like, particular things I should watch out for, so that doesn't, like, move in a general sense. Like, maybe specific things that are, like, specific to, like, what Kai is, like, looking for, that should maybe make sure I don't waste too much time. If it doesn't support this, I'll just leave this, and it'll go on to the next one.
Antoine Beaugas: Well, it's a bit hard,
Antoine Beaugas: The thing is, I am confident there's no simulator that can do everything.
Antoine Beaugas: And the point of this task is either to prove me right or wrong. Hopefully wrong, because we need a simulator, so I really hope someone can find one.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: So.
Antoine Beaugas: Any, any simulator you found, even if there's not everything.
Antoine Beaugas: Write what it has, what it hasn't, because it will be useful for later, for other research.
Antoine Beaugas: Because if you don't write audio research, like, for instance, there's Wokwi as a simulator. If nobody talks about Wokwi because you can't do everything.
Antoine Beaugas: If someone else will search.
Antoine Beaugas: They might search Wokwi, because it's not in the list, even though… It has already been searched.
Antoine Beaugas: So be sure to write everything.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, thank you.
Antoine Beaugas: Another source needs done. There's SAID.
Antoine Beaugas: Muhammad Said.
Antoine Beaugas: Are you here?
mohamed abdelmohsen: If you're asking only about Muhammad, I am Muhammad
mohamed abdelmohsen: If you want someone else, so you forget that until,
Antoine Beaugas: He isn't here, so I guess there's literally just one Mohammed. You were right since the beginning.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Well, he, he isn't here, unfortunately, can't do, can't do anything about it.
John Hazlewood: So, Syed, are you there?
John Hazlewood: Can you hear us, Syed?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Saeed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Muhammad Saeed.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Then aside.
Antoine Beaugas: No, not here.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay.
mohamed abdelmohsen: up in.
MOHAMED SAEED: Yeah, yeah, I'm now hearing this.
Antoine Beaugas: Come on.
Antoine Beaugas: you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Muhammad, they can't say Saeed. Man, this is the power of our Arabic language. They can't say Saeed, so if they say… Yeah, Saeed, you know, this letter? Ayim. They can say it. So, guys, I'm so sorry, but…
mohamed abdelmohsen: I'm trying to be humble, but this is the Arabic language. No one can, you know, speak it so.
MOHAMED SAEED: also.
mohamed abdelmohsen: It's nothing.
MOHAMED SAEED: I agree with you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So they mentioned you, my friend, since one hour ago. They talking Saeed Saad. Saeed Saad. So they talking about you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
MOHAMED SAEED: Yeah, awesome.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
MOHAMED SAEED: Awesome.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, so SAEED Do you have…
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: Have you received any hardware?
MOHAMED SAEED: Nature.
Antoine Beaugas: No, okay.
Antoine Beaugas: It's not quite important right now. What I think you'll help with is… is.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: The documentation, I don't remember, have you skills in electrical engineering?
MOHAMED SAEED: Electrical engineering.
Antoine Beaugas: Yes, electrical engineering.
Antoine Beaugas: Electricity.
MOHAMED SAEED: That is all.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, electronic circuits, current consumption and… This kind of thing.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
MOHAMED SAEED: Yeah, so…
Antoine Beaugas: So, there's… there's Jackie, who has a task. It's to…
Antoine Beaugas: Check in the documentation. The old members came up with.
Antoine Beaugas: an amount, certain amount of current consumption for Kaipo. It was 1.5… 1.5 amperes peak.
Antoine Beaugas: And I think it was 92 milliampere average.
Antoine Beaugas: So, you will help him?
Antoine Beaugas: Checking if it is right.
Antoine Beaugas: And if it is wrong, calculate the true value of the current consumption for Kaipo.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: the.
MOHAMED SAEED: I think you should.
Antoine Beaugas: should need…
MOHAMED SAEED: Yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: Yes?
Antoine Beaugas: Yes, repeat what you said.
MOHAMED SAEED: He will contact me at this port, or…
Antoine Beaugas: Contact him, I will tell him that
Antoine Beaugas: I will add you to the task.
Antoine Beaugas: And just send him a message, like, hi, we're working together.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
MOHAMED SAEED: Oh.
Antoine Beaugas: Because I sent him, like, some components, some links, I think, because he asked me questions.
Antoine Beaugas: So, he will be able to update you on the details.
Antoine Beaugas: So that's important that you work together on that.
Antoine Beaugas: So, okay, I'll, you would do that. You would be a signer.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, thank you.
Antoine Beaugas: And I think I went over everyone. Let me check.
Antoine Beaugas: A final time?
Antoine Beaugas: Chibuki Chizunuwa's name Joe like yes, I went over everyone.
Antoine Beaugas: So, to end the meeting, if Mohammed or John wants to say something, it's the right moment.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes, Antoine?
MOHAMED SAEED: you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: So guys.
mohamed abdelmohsen: First of all, Mr. John, I want to say some words. Antoine, I know we're missing some kind of, let's say.
MOHAMED SAEED: the.
mohamed abdelmohsen: tools you want right now, actually, with Kaibu. So, what we are missing right now, so we can purchase as soon as possible before you move?
Antoine Beaugas: I have to… it won't really matter if I move or not, because I will be using the hardware before a while.
Antoine Beaugas: The design has to be reviewed first, so…
Antoine Beaugas: It's not that urgent, but what is missing is… A new battery?
MOHAMED SAEED: the.
Antoine Beaugas: An USB-C adapter?
Antoine Beaugas: And that's it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Can you just provide me a link, mister John?
Antoine Beaugas: I don't have the links. That's what I have to search for. That's what we're missing. I have the other three components.
Antoine Beaugas: that they choose.
Antoine Beaugas: But I will still need a new battery, select a new battery and a USB adapter.
Antoine Beaugas: It will be 5 components to order, total.
MOHAMED SAEED: Okay.
John Hazlewood: Can you get… can you find those so we can order them? Either later today or tomorrow, Antoine?
Antoine Beaugas: Tomorrow, maybe I'll be able to have those.
Antoine Beaugas: Or at the latest, Thursday.
Antoine Beaugas: At the latest.
John Hazlewood: Okay, see what you can do so we can get those ordered and get them shipped. The last time we ordered, I think we paid extra to get some stuff shipped over here, and I think we still have something that's waiting here that you haven't gotten, right?
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, the… I don't remember how it's called, the Evaluation Board for the Power Management Integrated Circuits.
Antoine Beaugas: For testing with, with this.
Antoine Beaugas: With the wires and all.
John Hazlewood: And once you have that, is that… I think you mentioned that you were going to work on that with Sosina?
Antoine Beaugas: No, no, the… it was for the charger, the charger, you remember?
Antoine Beaugas: It was this for for Sosina.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: No, no, the evaluation board is to test for the prototype with the battery to test
Antoine Beaugas: If it works well with the battery, to test how to control it with the ESP, everything.
Antoine Beaugas: So it would be, maybe, the prototype number 2. I think the prototype number 1
Antoine Beaugas: Will be the software, mainly, and the sensors, and the prototype number 2 will be the battery and the power management.
Antoine Beaugas: I think we… I won't be here anymore, so Sabri should talk about it. I don't know when he'll be back, but…
Antoine Beaugas: Yes.
mohamed abdelmohsen: We're gonna miss you, Antoine.
Antoine Beaugas: You seem to miss.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Human.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yes.
Antoine Beaugas: What I want to do before I leave is to leave with
Antoine Beaugas: The… all the design for Kaipo.
Antoine Beaugas: clean and… Completed.
Antoine Beaugas: Like that, you won't have any more issues.
Antoine Beaugas: Hopefully, with it.
Antoine Beaugas: You will be able to follow the design.
Antoine Beaugas: Basically, my K-Pro out of it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Okay.
John Hazlewood: We won't be able to have a working prototype?
Antoine Beaugas: With the.
Antoine Beaugas: The documentation we had, the version 0.1, you wouldn't have… you wouldn't have
Antoine Beaugas: Been able to get a Vulkan prototype.
Antoine Beaugas: There's important information missing.
Antoine Beaugas: And you would have been blocked at some point, because there were some… Big errors in it.
John Hazlewood: Well, I mean, that was in the past. What about the… what about now? What about having.
Antoine Beaugas: What happened now? We're working on it. We're fixing everything we can.
Antoine Beaugas: like, the new diagram I showed at the beginning of the meeting, the new components I've chosen.
Antoine Beaugas: The current consumption, others are working on.
Antoine Beaugas: We are fixing everything.
John Hazlewood: And are we getting the five components that you talked about?
John Hazlewood: Is that gonna be, like, the hardware needed to have…
Antoine Beaugas: Zoom.
John Hazlewood: Thank you, Prototype.
Antoine Beaugas: Yep, That will be the updated power management circuits.
John Hazlewood: Okay, and then with that, we'll be able to connect to, say, ChatGPT and API from ChatGPT?
Antoine Beaugas: Well, this is the Raspberry and backend part of the project, and Sabri is way more skilled about it than I.
Antoine Beaugas: But the new components… Have nothing to do with it. It's really the poor management to have a…
Antoine Beaugas: A wireless capo.
Antoine Beaugas: With the battery.
Antoine Beaugas: Because, for now, you can… well, aside from the issues in the documentation that prevents us to program KEPO, because there's also issues that prevents us to program it, not only the hardware.
Antoine Beaugas: But basically, you can keep everything plugged in the computer.
Antoine Beaugas: And it will work without a battery, but you need to plug it.
Antoine Beaugas: And so to have Kaipo on your chest.
Antoine Beaugas: You need the components I'm choosing.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
John Hazlewood: So, it sounds like that's our top priority, is to get those components and
John Hazlewood: Make sure we have something that's… working.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, well.
Antoine Beaugas: There's also the fact that we started development of the first prototype, and it's blocked because informations are either wrong or missing in the documentation, so that's the biggest priority.
Antoine Beaugas: That's why I'm working on the diagrams.
Antoine Beaugas: Because we need them.
Antoine Beaugas: And after that, I will, some members will be able to resume work on Kaipo.
Antoine Beaugas: And I will search the battery and USB connector.
Antoine Beaugas: And we'll be able to order everything.
Antoine Beaugas: So I should finish the diagrams tomorrow, and that's why I said that at the latest, I should find the missing components Thursday.
Antoine Beaugas: It would depend on if I finish tomorrow early or late.
John Hazlewood: Okay, so I think in in order to have some continuity and
John Hazlewood: And, you know, the documentation that you're working on
John Hazlewood: I don't know who else here can maybe help and…
John Hazlewood: You know, be part of that, so,
Antoine Beaugas: Well, basically, pretty much everyone.
Antoine Beaugas: Aside from the new members who work on,
Antoine Beaugas: on researching a simulator. Like, I worked on the… on one of the diagrams with, With Ash.
Antoine Beaugas: I have now two people working on checking the current consumption.
Antoine Beaugas: This is also part of the documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: The research.
Antoine Beaugas: The resources in Adid for reducing the booting time… the boot time of the Raspberry is also part of the documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: So all of the little tasks I give here and there, it's for the documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: So, everyone is helping me right now, basically.
John Hazlewood: Okay, so everybody has tasks based on their time schedule to fill up their time that they have available.
John Hazlewood: And…
John Hazlewood: you know, so we can, like, next week, we've accomplished a lot of this stuff, and we can kind of get to the next stage, because I keep asking for, like, the document that Sabri put together.
John Hazlewood: at one time, and he presented on a Sunday meeting with, here are the tasks that need to get done, these are the things that need to get done so we can, you know, have our working prototype.
John Hazlewood: And, you know, I don't know, I guess you haven't been able to find that documentation or put something together or find the video recording, you know, but…
John Hazlewood: You know, I'm not really, like,
John Hazlewood: Yeah, having… being in these meetings and not being able to see a visualization of what the tasks are that we need to complete in order to get this thing to get a prototype
John Hazlewood: It's very difficult for me. I don't have knowledge that you have.
Antoine Beaugas: Sure.
Antoine Beaugas: Well, this document… Well, it was the document…
Antoine Beaugas: Before finding out we were going into a hole.
Antoine Beaugas: Because it's still… it's still right, the document is still right, the list of tasks.
Antoine Beaugas: But now, on top of all that, we have to fix the documentation, because the tasks that are left to do are blocked.
Antoine Beaugas: By this wrong documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: And by working on different parts of the documentation, it will unlock one by one those tasks. Like, the diagrams I'm working on currently with Ash.
Antoine Beaugas: It will unlock… The state machine of Kaipu.
Antoine Beaugas: There's a task in Sabri's list, develop the state machine. When the diagrams will be done, it will unlock that task. It will be possible to work on it.
Antoine Beaugas: So, this, the stabilized document for now is frozen because we literally can't work on those tasks.
Antoine Beaugas: And I'm working towards Unlocking those tasks one by one with the documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: basically. So yeah.
John Hazlewood: Okay, well, you know, I'm not sure who, like, I know HASANE has some time available. I don't know, HASANE, if you can maybe look at the documentation and participate in that.
John Hazlewood: Since you're gonna be with us for a while, and you're full-time, and, you know, we need to have some people that kind of have a really good understanding
John Hazlewood: Of what the documentation is, what we've been working on, what we need to do to launch and move things forward from, you know, the working prototype to…
John Hazlewood: You know, the next version after that, and yeah, and I'm not really…
John Hazlewood: You know, other than Sabri, who's having, you know, some…
John Hazlewood: Electricity issues in the village that he lives.
John Hazlewood: You know, I'm not really… we gotta involve some other people in this, and Austin, I think you're kind of…
John Hazlewood: Have a lot of.
HASNAE: Yeah.
John Hazlewood: and maybe.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
HASNAE: I, I, I think I must do some efforts.
HASNAE: And, from the meeting I'll be doing with Antoine.
HASNAE: to understand more of the architecture of the project, because being new to the project, I don't know where to find all the resources.
HASNAE: So, when we do the meeting, I will, I will ask him all the questions I had in mind, where I can find all the documents, where are the newest ones, the…
HASNAE: the license updates, The path, the pathway they were following.
HASNAE: Maybe some next steps, or some blocked steps.
HASNAE: And I can go forward doing this learning.
HASNAE: By doing…
John Hazlewood: Okay, I think that sounds good, and you know, like, one of the things that we need to be working on is our master class. The IoT team for as…
John Hazlewood: complex as IoT is and what we're doing, you know, our master class is, like, not very rich.
John Hazlewood: And, like, all this documentation… You know, before anybody starts.
John Hazlewood: you know, even starts working on a task. That should be, like, the first thing in the master class to review all the documentation, have some questions that people are responding to, to make sure that they know that documentation.
John Hazlewood: I mean, without reading the documentation, there's no reason why people should even work on a task if they don't know, like, that's the thing that everybody's gonna understand what's going on, and, you know, so…
HASNAE: Yes.
HASNAE: Yeah, I agree because while working on my research today, I observed that working with Notion is like a…
HASNAE: diving with a tree, a tree with so many branches, and you… every single page of Notion
HASNAE: Drive you to another page, and you get so easily, easily confused by the amount of pages, and, not knowing which one is the accurate, most important documents, and, others that, are not.
Antoine Beaugas: Well, it's simple. For now, there's no correct documents because the correct document is under construction.
Antoine Beaugas: That's why it's not in the masterclass, because I see no points in making the interns lose 50 hours reading wrong documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: That's why, basically.
HASNAE: Yeah, but at the end, they… at the end, we…
HASNAE: We can't read it, because otherwise we don't… you can't understand the whole project, technically speaking.
HASNAE: Without doing so, so… I think at the end you just need to read all of the content existing.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, I can add it to the masterclass. Maybe…
Antoine Beaugas: Have you checked in the… in your team home? What I… wait, I'm… I will share my screen.
Antoine Beaugas: Your team home, you see?
HASNAE: the.
Antoine Beaugas: In the team home, I put some important information.
Antoine Beaugas: Usefully.
HASNAE: is.
Antoine Beaugas: with the GitHub repository, Linux Basics, ESP-IDF documentation, there's some documentation here.
HASNAE: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: The wrong documentation, for instance, you see?
HASNAE: Yeah, I'm sorry, it's the first time I saw this.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, that's why, because… You can't tell me, not you particularly, I mean, generally speaking, you can't tell me.
Antoine Beaugas: I don't have any documents when I put some efforts making everything available in the team room.
Antoine Beaugas: So… so…
HASNAE: That means.
Antoine Beaugas: We need to find a way to make the new members know
Antoine Beaugas: The system of team homes in the company.
HASNAE: Exactly.
Antoine Beaugas: Because if the interns know, okay, each team has a team home, let's take a look at them, and interacting team home, documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: So, we should find a way to make sure the new members know about this.
John Hazlewood: Well, well, it… I think any documentation in whatever team it is.
John Hazlewood: You know, if it's important documentation, it either needs to be assigned as a task for them to read or it needs to be put into the masterclass.
John Hazlewood: So whatever's basic that everybody has to do should be, you know, part of the onboarding the master class. If
John Hazlewood: you know.
John Hazlewood: So, yeah, and then things that pop up, you know, that are new things, then they should be assigned.
John Hazlewood: to the current team, and then if that stuff goes into the map, needs to go into existing documentation that's part of the masterclass for new people, then they would see that. But existing people would need a task assigned, because now we've got some new stuff that they need to see.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, you just gave me an idea. It's to make a task, check the team room.
Antoine Beaugas: and read the documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah. You give the task to each new member, and they come here, they see, okay, so this is the team home, there's links, and read, like, KPO version 0.1 documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: Walter.
John Hazlewood: For everybody now that hasn't done that, they should receive a task. And for all the new people that are going to join from today forward, it should be part of the masterclass. They don't need to be assigned a task, they just… there needs to be… and it's not just read this, it's read this and answer these questions.
Antoine Beaugas: Oh, yeah, yeah, like, put the link of the team home in the masterclass, and yeah, we can do that, yeah. Yeah, yeah.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, yeah, and make sure that there's some questions for each one to, like… so they kind of, like, what are the important things for them to get out of it, so they read it, and then…
John Hazlewood: You know, they can add some information
John Hazlewood: Maybe there's some suggestions on how we can improve it.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, also because I've asked this multiple times already, if you have ideas on how to make it better. So having it in the masterclass would be a very efficient way of having feedbacks and new ideas.
Antoine Beaugas: So, yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: Completely.
Antoine Beaugas: Should add the link to the.
Antoine Beaugas: To the masterclass, and prepare questions, yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: Of course.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, well, whoever hasn't done that that's in this team right now, or is…
John Hazlewood: you know, has joined and is not here in this meeting today, then, you know, make sure that… I mean.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, that should be, like… The first thing that everybody's working on, I mean…
John Hazlewood: Of course, whatever tasks you have, work on whatever… work on those tasks, but if you haven't read the documentation, you know, that's like…
John Hazlewood: You know.
John Hazlewood: You gotta have context.
John Hazlewood: So…
Antoine Beaugas: Yep.
John Hazlewood: Okay.
Antoine Beaugas: I'm writing it down to not forget about it in my in my notes.
Antoine Beaugas: And, I'll do that. I will add the…
Antoine Beaugas: the team home link in the masterclass, and I'll have to prepare questions.
Antoine Beaugas: And I will ask, if we want to check the team home and… We'll see what's inside, basically.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, and Chizalum and Chibuke.
John Hazlewood: You guys have any thoughts about what we're talking about?
Antoine Beaugas: ask.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: I would say most of it is clear.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Yeah, I would say it was a very good idea to actually, like, involve that team room in the master class, so that one has access to everything. That's, like, so they can, like…
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: Be cut up to speed, because…
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: even after the master class, after I got my first module, like, okay, I'm going to research a lot of things, but what is the current like?
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: what exactly are the requirements I need to use and test all this? So it was a bit confusing at first.
Chizalum Cele-Ughanze: So I'll say that's a good idea to have that team room available in the masterclass.
John Hazlewood: Okay, okay, great.
John Hazlewood: Great. Thank you. Said.
John Hazlewood: So, any thoughts?
John Hazlewood: Feedback from you?
MOHAMED SAEED: Actually, no.
John Hazlewood: No.
John Hazlewood: Okay. Michael, have you gotten a chance to read through that documentation? You've been here for a while.
John Hazlewood: So I don't know whether you've actually gone through it at all in the past.
Michael Ballantyne: I did go through it when Sabri was pointing out how he… everything was supposed to be done, but that was back with the old documentation, so I'll have to revisit it.
Michael Ballantyne: And just.
Antoine Beaugas: That we did.
Antoine Beaugas: Yes, I've already made a task at the time for everyone, but we were, like, 4 or 5 members.
Antoine Beaugas: So…
John Hazlewood: I think what's important right now… With Antoine…
John Hazlewood: finishing here with his internship is, you know, all hands on deck to go through that documentation and deep dive.
John Hazlewood: Plug that into Notion, plug that into ChatGPT.
John Hazlewood: Figure out what's missing. Come up with questions. Start discussing internally.
John Hazlewood: We need to prioritize updating that documentation. That's our number one priority.
John Hazlewood: We gotta get, you know, the organization is that documentation.
John Hazlewood: And we don't want Antoine to leave, and we still don't know, and maybe he knew something, and now we gotta get ahold of him, and, you know, he's in class or whatever, and so, you know, we want to get everything done now. That's… that should be, like.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and then… And have… so, yeah, everybody please go through that in detail.
John Hazlewood: Don't skim it, read it in detail.
John Hazlewood: If you're questioning something should be in there, something's wrong, you know, highlight it, get back to Antoine, get back to the team. Let's use the… in the chat group.
John Hazlewood: with the IoT team to go back and put things there so everybody can see if anyone has any thoughts about the documentation, so we can engage everybody together to kind of
John Hazlewood: Look at that, yeah, so the documentation, and then just making sure that this next
John Hazlewood: These parts that we order, We get something that's…
John Hazlewood: That's hopefully gonna gonna work, because… It's weird.
Antoine Beaugas: It's with high confidence.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, well, we're gonna be celebrating. I'm gonna be taking you out to dinner before you leave Antoine
John Hazlewood: We gotta get, get that…
Antoine Beaugas: Oh. And don't hesitate if you're unsure about… if you're right about something being wrong in the documentation.
Antoine Beaugas: Don't be afraid to tell, oh, I think this is wrong, because if you're wrong, you will learn something, and if you're right, it will be great, because we need to fight all the issues, so…
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, don't be shy.
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and as soon as you guys go through that and upgrade it.
John Hazlewood: I want to plug it into ChatGPT. I just plugged in some of Indra's, architecture.
John Hazlewood: And it gave me a lot of improvements.
John Hazlewood: And you know, and we did the same thing on the previous documentation, of course, and I mean, I don't know you guys need to be doing that. It's like.
John Hazlewood: Plug that into ChatGBT and ask it.
John Hazlewood: You know, is this the best solution? Compare it to our competitors.
John Hazlewood: Research our competitive, you know, our competitors, you know, and Get, you know, like…
John Hazlewood: Make sure that it's clear to you guys. You guys are embedded systems.
John Hazlewood: You know.
John Hazlewood: I don't have the technical skills to kind of go in and really, you know, understand and ask ChatGPT the right questions to get the right feedback.
John Hazlewood: That's… that's your… your competence.
John Hazlewood: That's your area of expertise.
John Hazlewood: And so… Y'all need to be…
John Hazlewood: Tearing that apart, understanding it inside and out, So…
John Hazlewood: Yeah, and then once, you know, I wanted to do it too, after, like, hopefully by this time next week, we'll have kind of a version updated, and then, you know, I'd like to see what ChatGPT… ChatGPT is like history of
John Hazlewood: A lot of things I'm plugging in. I'm in front of ChatGBT, probably.
John Hazlewood: I don't know, 3, 4 hours a day. I was having long conversations with it today about stuff, and so it's kind of…
John Hazlewood: You know, I'm not…
John Hazlewood: I'm using it all the time for everything. I don't use… someone mentioned, oh, just Google this.
John Hazlewood: Google something. So Google, I was thinking to myself.
John Hazlewood: Is anyone still using Google?
John Hazlewood: Really?
John Hazlewood: In this… at Flo Labs, someone's using Google?
John Hazlewood: You know, like, we should be using ChatGBT!
John Hazlewood: use ChatGPT to ask it questions, whether you want to go somewhere or do whatever. If you're not using ChatGPT and you're still using Google, I don't know what to say. You know, but…
John Hazlewood: yeah, we we, you know, we're AI first, st and we have to like like Using these tools,
John Hazlewood: They, they… you know, I'm… I'm taking pictures of things, tell me how to do this.
John Hazlewood: I mean, it's like, I can't… like, for me, Kaipo is, like, it's gonna be so helpful, it's gonna… I don't have to pull out my phone and take a picture of something, or, you know, I can just wear it and ask it, you know, because I'm a power user for AI. Maybe you guys aren't power users, but…
John Hazlewood: You know, I'm just…
John Hazlewood: For me, and I think for everybody in the future, everybody's gonna be an AI power user.
John Hazlewood: It's just gonna be…
John Hazlewood: like, everyone's using their cell phone, bending over, and has back issues like I do, you know, and it's just gonna be… You know, just natural.
John Hazlewood: So…
John Hazlewood: Okay, thank you so much. We're making some progress, Antoine, slowly but surely. We just need to kind of try to speed things up right now, between now and the next 7 days. So, next week we can…
John Hazlewood: You know, have some…
John Hazlewood: Substantial progress, and hopefully we've got all the parts here from those five components, and maybe you can show us something working.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, well, the components, as I said, won't be in use for a bit of time.
Antoine Beaugas: Because it's the poor management system, and before that, we need Why do we need a.
Antoine Beaugas: Kaipu.
Antoine Beaugas: in itself, before.
John Hazlewood: Okay, well, let's knock those out in parallel.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah.
Antoine Beaugas: We'll see.
John Hazlewood: So… Okay, all right, Antoine, thank you. Thank you. Everybody.
Antoine Beaugas: Yes, thank you for being here.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Yeah, go ahead, Antoine.
Antoine Beaugas: No, just thank you for being here for this meeting. Thank you.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Man, I'm gonna miss you. I'm gonna miss you. Oh my gosh, like six months has run away, man. Like.
mohamed abdelmohsen: What is happening?
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Hopefully one day I can come to France. Where do you live in France? Excellent one.
Antoine Beaugas: I don't know what I'll do with my life.
Antoine Beaugas: I don't know where…
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh.
Antoine Beaugas: In which company?
Antoine Beaugas: I don't know. I have nothing planned.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Oh my gosh. You're gonna figure it out. Don't worry.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: As soon as you settle down, my friend, don't forget to give us invitation for your marriage, hopefully.
Antoine Beaugas: it.
mohamed abdelmohsen: I think this is the only way that I can meet you, maybe by one day. But don't forget, you're gonna pay for my ticket.
mohamed abdelmohsen: You could you? Yes, man, you're gonna pay for it.
Antoine Beaugas: Yeah, yeah.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Now he will not invite me. Okay. Thank you, Antoine.
mohamed abdelmohsen: No, Susan.
Antoine Beaugas: Okay, meeting's over. Thank you.
Antoine Beaugas: You're free.
mohamed abdelmohsen: Everyone.